# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create( name: 'Star Wars' ,  name: 'Lord of the Rings' )
#   Character.create(name: 'Luke', movie: movies.first)


q1 = Question.create(question: 'What is the proper term for a group of kittens?', answer1: 'Kaboodle', answer2: 'Kine', answer3: 'Kettle', answer4: 'Kindle', correct_answer: 'Kindle')
q2 = Question.create(question: 'All cats are born with what color eyes?', answer1: 'Black', answer2: 'Blue', answer3: 'Pink', answer4: 'Green', correct_answer: 'Blue')
q3 = Question.create(question: 'What percentage of a cat\'s bones are in its tail?', answer1: 'There are no bones in a cat\'s tail', answer2: '20%', answer3: '10%', answer4: '2%', correct_answer: '10%')
q4 = Question.create(question: 'What is it called when a cat kneads the ground?', answer1: 'Sneegling', answer2: 'Rubbing', answer3: 'Snurgling', answer4: 'Kneading', correct_answer: 'Snurgling')
q5 = Question.create(question: 'How many different sounds can a cat make?', answer1: '150', answer2: '10', answer3: '100', answer4: '27', correct_answer: '100')
q6 = Question.create(question: 'How many breeds of domestic cat are there worldwide?', answer1: '70', answer2: '210', answer3: '140', answer4: '280', correct_answer: '70')
q7 = Question.create(question: 'What year was the first major cat show held in the United States?', answer1: '1895', answer2: '1921', answer3: '1952', answer4: '1842', correct_answer: '1895')
q8 = Question.create(question: 'What is the normal body temperature of a cat?', answer1: '98 degrees F', answer2: '94 degrees F', answer3: '102 degrees F', answer4: '106 degrees F', correct_answer: '102 degrees F')
q9 = Question.create(question: 'What breed of cat has a reputation for being cross-eyed?', answer1: 'Egyptian Mau', answer2: 'Himalayan', answer3: 'Siamese', answer4: 'Persian', correct_answer: 'Siamese')
q10 = Question.create(question: 'If a male cat is both orange and black, he is probably...?', answer1: 'Schizophrenic', answer2: 'Sterile', answer3: 'Deaf', answer4: 'Blind', correct_answer: 'Sterile')

q11 = Question.create(question: 'What breed of cat has no tail?', answer1: 'Snowshow', answer2: 'Manx', answer3: 'La Perm', answer4: 'Singapura', correct_answer: 'Manx')
q12 = Question.create(question: 'What breed of domestic cat has the longest fur?', answer1: 'Persian', answer2: 'Sphynx', answer3: 'Tonkinese', answer4: 'Himalayan', correct_answer: 'Persian')
q13 = Question.create(question: 'Which U.S. city had a cat for a mayor for almost 20 years?', answer1: 'Jacksboro, Texas', answer2: 'Talkeetna, Alaska', answer3: 'Warm River, Idaho', answer4: 'Gardner, Kansas', correct_answer: 'Talkeetna, Alaska')
q14 = Question.create(question: 'Which country has more cats per person than any other country in the world?', answer1: 'Denmark', answer2: 'New Zealand', answer3: 'United States', answer4: 'Djibouti', correct_answer: 'New Zealand')
q15 = Question.create(question: 'How many cats did Abraham Lincoln have in the White House?', answer1: '1', answer2: '4', answer3: '3', answer4: '2', correct_answer: '4')
q16 = Question.create(question: 'What skill do cats develop when playing with yarn/toys?', answer1: 'Socializing', answer2: 'Mating', answer3: 'Finding Food', answer4: 'Hunting', correct_answer: 'Hunting')
q17 = Question.create(question: 'What is a group of cats called?', answer1: 'Chowder', answer2: 'Clowder', answer3: 'Cluster', answer4: 'Felis', correct_answer: 'Clowder')
q18 = Question.create(question: 'What is the extreme fear of cats called?', answer1: 'Katsaridaphobia', answer2: 'Consecotaleophobia', answer3: 'Anatidaephobia', answer4: 'Ailurophobia', correct_answer: 'Ailurophobia')
q19 = Question.create(question: 'What is the largest breed of cats?', answer1: 'Maine Coon', answer2: 'British Shorthair', answer3: 'Savannah', answer4: 'Ragdoll', correct_answer: 'Maine Coons')
q20 = Question.create(question: 'What percent of people identify as cat people?', answer1: '27.9%', answer2: '34.6%', answer3: '11.5%', answer4: '48.2%', correct_answer: '11.5%')

q21 = Question.create(question: 'How many teeth does an adult cat have?', answer1: '32', answer2: '30', answer3: '36', answer4: '24', correct_answer: '30')
q22 = Question.create(question: 'How much did the world\'s heaviest cat weigh?', answer1: '53 lbs.', answer2: '41 lbs.', answer3: '59 lbs.', answer4: '47 lbs.', correct_answer: '47 lbs.')
q23 = Question.create(question: 'What cartoon cat is buddies with a dog named Odie?', answer1: 'Garfield', answer2: 'Felix', answer3: 'Sylvester', answer4: 'Heathcliff', correct_answer: 'Garfield')
q24 = Question.create(question: 'How fast can cats run?', answer1: '30 MPH', answer2: '40 MPH', answer3: '50 MPH', answer4: '20 MPH', correct_answer: '30 MPH')
q25 = Question.create(question: 'How many times are cats mentioned in the Hebrew Bible?', answer1: '27', answer2: '49', answer3: '12', answer4: '0', correct_answer: '0')
q26 = Question.create(question: 'Who was the first cat launched in space?', answer1: 'Veronique', answer2: 'Felicette', answer3: 'Felix', answer4: 'Laika', correct_answer: 'Felicette')
q27 = Question.create(question: 'Why do cats rub against you?', answer1: 'To mark you with its scent', answer2: 'To say hello', answer3: 'All of these', answer4: 'To show affection', correct_answer: 'All of these')
q28 = Question.create(question: 'What breed of cat has individual hairs banded with different colors?', answer1: 'Persian', answer2: 'Maine Coon', answer3: 'British Shorthair', answer4: 'Abyssinian', correct_answer: 'Abyssinian')
q29 = Question.create(question: 'Which of these foods is toxic to cats?', answer1: 'All of these', answer2: 'Grapes', answer3: 'Onions', answer4: 'Chocolate', correct_answer: 'All of these')
q30 = Question.create(question: 'What cat has fur so dense you can draw patterns in its coat?', answer1: 'Tonkinese', answer2: 'Ragdoll', answer3: 'Russian Blue', answer4: 'Turkish Angora', correct_answer: 'Russian Blue')

q31 = Question.create(question: 'What is the smallest breed of cat?', answer1: 'Munchkin', answer2: 'Sphynx', answer3: 'Singapura', answer4: 'Cornish Rex', correct_answer: 'Singapura')
q32 = Question.create(question: 'What Catholic Pope condemned cats as evil?', answer1: 'Pius VII', answer2: 'Julius III', answer3: 'Gregory XIII', answer4: 'Innocent VIII', correct_answer: 'Innocent VIII')
q33 = Question.create(question: 'How many hours do cats sleep every day?', answer1: '12-16', answer2: '8-12', answer3: '20-24', answer4: '16-20', correct_answer: '16-20')
q34 = Question.create(question: 'How did ancient Egyptians mourn when a family cat died?', answer1: 'Shave their eyebrows', answer2: 'Sacrifice a dog', answer3: 'Eat no food for three days', answer4: 'Throw a party', correct_answer: 'Shave their eyebrows')
q35 = Question.create(question: 'How old was the world\'s oldest cat?', answer1: '38', answer2: '40', answer3: '34', answer4: '36', correct_answer: '38')
q36 = Question.create(question: 'How many kittens can a single pair of cats and their offspring produce in 7 years?', answer1: '66,000', answer2: '370,000', answer3: '12,000', answer4: '2,072,000', correct_answer: '370,000')
q37 = Question.create(question: 'How many whiskers does a cat have?', answer1: '18', answer2: '36', answer3: '24', answer4: '12', correct_answer: '24')
q38 = Question.create(question: 'What was the name of Geppetto\'s cat in Disney\'s "Pinocchio"', answer1: 'Figaro', answer2: 'Stromboli', answer3: 'Jiminy', answer4: 'Lampwick', correct_answer: 'Figaro')
q39 = Question.create(question: 'How many people are bitten by cats in the U.S. each year?', answer1: '400,000', answer2: '4,000', answer3: '40,000', answer4: '4,000,000', correct_answer: '400,000')
q40 = Question.create(question: 'What do cats have on their front legs, but not on their hind legs?', answer1: 'Tibiofibular joint', answer2: 'Dewclaw', answer3: 'Femur', answer4: 'Tarsal bones', correct_answer: 'Dewclaw')

q41 = Question.create(question: 'Why do cats lick themselves?', answer1: 'To keep wounds clean', answer2: 'To evenly distribute natural oils', answer3: 'To stimulate blood flow', answer4: 'All of these', correct_answer: 'All of these')
q42 = Question.create(question: 'How far can a cat fall without dying?', answer1: '3 stories', answer2: '7 stories', answer3: '19 stories', answer4: 'Any height', correct_answer: 'Any height')
q43 = Question.create(question: 'Who was the first cartoon cat?', answer1: 'Felix', answer2: 'Pistol Pete', answer3: 'Garfield', answer4: 'Heathcliff', correct_answer: 'Felix')
q44 = Question.create(question: 'How many colors of Ocicat are approved by most registries?', answer1: '12', answer2: '6', answer3: '8', answer4: '10', correct_answer: '12')
q45 = Question.create(question: 'What is the earliest known ancestor of the modern cat?', answer1: 'Aeluropuss', answer2: 'Proailurus', answer3: 'Gheerfelis', answer4: 'Rukwalorax', correct_answer: 'Proailurus')
q46 = Question.create(question: 'Where do cats have most of their sweat glands?', answer1: 'Ears', answer2: 'Nose', answer3: 'Bellies', answer4: 'Paws', correct_answer: 'Paws')
q47 = Question.create(question: 'What causes cat allergies?', answer1: 'All of these', answer2: 'Dander', answer3: 'Dried saliva', answer4: 'Uring', correct_answer: 'All of these')
q48 = Question.create(question: 'What was the punsihment for smuggling a cat out of ancient Egypt?', answer1: 'Exile', answer2: 'Life in prison', answer3: 'Death', answer4: 'Hand chopped off', correct_answer: 'Death')
q49 = Question.create(question: 'What is a female cat called?', answer1: 'Dame', answer2: 'Bitch', answer3: 'Queen', answer4: 'Doe', correct_answer: 'Queen')
q50 = Question.create(question: 'How many muscles does a cat have in each year?', answer1: '32', answer2: '20', answer3: '6', answer4: '48', correct_answer: '32')

q51 = Question.create(question: 'What was the name of the first cloned cat?', answer1: 'CC', answer2: 'Max', answer3: 'Little Nicky', answer4: 'Chance', correct_answer: 'CC')
q52 = Question.create(question: 'What Cat Goddess did ancient Egyptians worship?', answer1: 'Anuket', answer2: 'Bastet', answer3: 'Isis', answer4: 'Heket', correct_answer: 'Bastet')
q53 = Question.create(question: 'What is the name of Homer Simpson\'s cat?', answer1: 'Itchy', answer2: 'Scratchy', answer3: 'Santa\'s Little Helper', answer4: 'Snowball', correct_answer: 'Snowball')
q54 = Question.create(question: 'How many hairs does a cat have per square inch on its belly?', answer1: '12,000', answer2: '24,000', answer3: '60,000', answer4: '120,000', correct_answer: '120,000')
q55 = Question.create(question: 'Tabby cats are named after a neighborhood in what city?', answer1: 'Rio de Janeiro', answer2: 'Liverpool', answer3: 'New York', answer4: 'Baghdad', correct_answer: 'Baghdad')
q56 = Question.create(question: 'What is another name for the cougar?', answer1: 'Catamount', answer2: 'All of these', answer3: 'Puma', answer4: 'Mountain Lion', correct_answer: 'All of these')
q57 = Question.create(question: 'What breed of cat is known for its "owl-like" appearance?', answer1: 'Devon Rex', answer2: 'Norwegian Forest Cat', answer3: 'Scottish Fold', answer4: 'Turkish Angora', correct_answer: 'Scottish Fold')
q58 = Question.create(question: 'Which of the following was a prehistoric subfamily of cats?', answer1: 'Borophaginae', answer2: 'Machairodontinae', answer3: 'Simocyoninae', answer4: 'Hesperocyonines', correct_answer: 'Machairodontinae')
q59 = Question.create(question: 'What kind of cat did surrealist painter Salvador Dali keep as a pet?', answer1: 'Serval', answer2: 'Lynx', answer3: 'Caracal', answer4: 'Ocelot', correct_answer: 'Ocelot')
q60 = Question.create(question: 'In Thailand, what cat is given to newlyweds for good luck?', answer1: 'Chartreux', answer2: 'Cymric Cat', answer3: 'Manx', answer4: 'Korat', correct_answer: 'Korat')

q61 = Question.create(question: 'What cat is nicknamed "the gentle giant"?', answer1: 'Savannah', answer2: 'Maine Coon', answer3: 'Burmese', answer4: 'Ragdoll', correct_answer: 'Korat')
q62 = Question.create(question: 'Which of the following cat breeds is considered hypoallergenic?', answer1: 'Siberian', answer2: 'Balinese', answer3: 'All of these', answer4: 'Siberian', correct_answer: 'All of these')
q63 = Question.create(question: 'What cat is called the "tree tiger" in Indonesia?', answer1: 'Lynx', answer2: 'Serval', answer3: 'Puma', answer4: 'Clouded Leopard', correct_answer: 'Clouded Leopard')
q64 = Question.create(question: 'What breed of cat has no hair except for down?', answer1: 'Egyptian Mau', answer2: 'Scottish Fold', answer3: 'Cornish Rex', answer4: 'Russian Blue', correct_answer: 'Cornish Rex')
q65 = Question.create(question: 'What domestic cat was bred to resemble a tiger?', answer1: 'Shardui', answer2: 'Tigger', answer3: 'Striped Shorthair', answer4: 'Toyger', correct_answer: 'Toyger')
q66 = Question.create(question: 'Which subfamily of cats includes the tiger?', answer1: 'Felinae', answer2: 'Barbourofelidae', answer3: 'Pantherinae', answer4: 'Simocyoninae', correct_answer: 'Pantherinae')
q67 = Question.create(question: 'What cat is distinguished by the extreme depression of the skull, which extends along the nose to the extremity of the muzzle?', answer1: 'Flat-headed Cat', answer2: 'Persian Leopard', answer3: 'Sunda Clouded Leopard', answer4: 'Bay Cat', correct_answer: 'Flat-headed Cat')

